(Space Rice Cake)
(The saviour for the exhausted Earth Arcaders)
(Part-timer Gabee arrived.)
(Right from her first order, she radiated cheerful energy...)
(and showed off her cheeky, pleasant humour.)
(The customers fell for the part-timer's charm.)
(It's fun...)
(so far.)
(This one has only 2 shrimps...)
(whereas that one has 3 shrimps.)
(Starting with a complaint...)
(Please let there be 5 or more here.)
(Please let me see 5 or more when I lift this up.)
(They were running short on rice cake buns.)
(There's nowhere to fall back to.)
(Just when they thought things couldn't get any worse...)
(Clattering)
(Yu Jin even dropped a burger on the floor.)
(The dinner rush isn't going well. Could they wrap things up smoothly?)
They came out beautifully. They look so great.
(The 12 "Welsh Corgis" are finally good to go.)
I'm just naturally talented.
- Did you fall on the stairs? - Is this for real?
- No. I put one on the table first. - Yes.
I mean, I had two burgers on the tray.
The moment I took one off, the tray lost its balance.
- Oh, no. - Oh, boy.
- The tray lost its balance. - I see.
I guess two burgers on a tray are all I can handle.
Right, Yu Jin. Be careful.
I'll make it quickly.
- Thank you. - Be sure not to get hurt.
By the way, I'm so happy...
that Neapolitan Matfia said it was tasty.
- Exactly, Young Ji. You crushed it. - Yes, I did.
I wish he had ordered pizza and the other things...
I wish he had tried your tteoksagna. It was really good.
- My point exactly. - Your tteoksagna.
(And meanwhile...)
(Gabee is quietly getting her job done.)
- Gabee, are you doing all right? - Of course.
I'm doing great. I'm washing this right now.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- I'm washing the dishcloth. - Thank you.
Don't worry. I love it.
I love my job.
(She says the same phrases, but in a less cheerful tone.)
She's so sweet. She has such a good heart.
I know, right?
She doesn't want to make us worry.
- She has such a fabulous mindset. - Right.
(Chuckling)
- Gabee, thank you so much. - Yes?
Don't mention it. This is fun.
Gabee, let's chant together. Ahk.
- Ahk. - Ahk.
- I don't know what that means. - You don't know what it means.
- Let's go. - She's a total smile fairy.
(While the one with a "fabulous mindset" is doing a great job...)
There's a cutlery station upstairs.
You can take the cutlery there.
- And please put this on your table. - I see.
Thank you.
- One of it... - Yes.
- and 1 pomegranate ade. - And 1 pomegranate ade.
Table 11 ordered 1 original tteokbokki,
one pizza,
one shrimp burger, one beef burger,
and one carrot cake.
And one extra pomegranate ade.
- We got a new order. - Okay.
One margarita, one ade,
one carrot cake, one pizza,
one tteokbokki, one shrimp burger,
- and one beef burger. - They're having everything.
- They're having one of everything. - They're having everything.
(Burger Status: 3 beef burgers including the 1 that dropped,)
(three shrimp burgers)
I got the buns ready.
- Take your time. - You're amazing as always.
(She cooks 3 patties at the same time.)
(Now that she's gotten a compliment from her master...)
(She presses the patty confidently.)
One shrimp burger is out.
- Three beef burgers. - Three shrimp burgers.
Two shrimp burgers, Mimi.
Two more shrimp burgers.
Which shrimp burger came out?
- The one before the new order? - Yes.
- Then you have two to go now. - Okay.
Our head chef is...
really good with numbers and has a good memory.
- I'm upset with you, though. - Why?
You don't pay attention when new orders come in.
That's not true. I do pay attention...
(Her inner thoughts she'd been bottling up burst out.)
- I'm sorry. - That's okay.
Relying on my own memory gives me peace of mind.
Thank you.
A sous chef's job is to follow the head chef's orders.
I'm grateful for your existence.
(Whenever she's upset, she reminds herself of their camaraderie.)
Cover these with basting domes, and we can play the shell game.
(The patties cooked with Young Ji's shell game skills...)
- Seriously. - Where is the shaker?
One beef burger is ready to replace the one Yu Jin dropped.
Here's a beef burger for the table that didn't get their order.
Thank you.
- Be careful not to fall, princess. - Be careful.
It could happen because the floor is slippery.
- You guys are lifesavers. - You have two more to go.
(Fuelled by those cheerful words, she's back on server duty.)
- Here's your burger. - Already?
Thank you.
- I'm sorry for the wait. - That's okay.
- It's okay. We'll enjoy this. - Please enjoy.
Thank you.
It looks good.
The cheese is melted to perfection.
(The replacement burger satisfies the customer.)
- The burger is good. - Right.
(Burger Status: One beef burger, served,)
(one shrimp burger, served)
(Once the satisfied customers leave,)
(they get ready for a new customer.)
It's still rewarding, isn't it?
- This is fun. - Indeed.
- You just keep going, you know. - Right.
(As they keep working on autopilot,)
(the dishes are piling up in the sink.)
What should I do with these?
It's so great to have Gabee here.
- It's so great. - Indeed.
Table 10 and Table 11.
- Table 10 and Table 11. - I feel bad saying this,
but I'm just so happy.
Lee Young Ji...
(She's repeating the orders nonstop.)
Lee Young Ji for Table Ten.
Lee Young Ji...
Lee Young Ji for Table 10 and Table 11.
What about "Lee Young Ji?"
Lee Young Ji for Table Ten.
A pomegranate ade for Table 11.
(Talking to herself)
(For some reason, she just wants to say Young Ji's name.)
(Tell me more, tell me more)
(And for some reason, Gabee's labour song feels sad.)
(Singing)
They've actually been doing a messy job.
Who would work like this?
Who would put trash in the sink?
(It was you.)
Goodness gracious.
(She's giving herself an earful.)
Two beef burger combos are ready.
One shrimp burger will be ready shortly.
(There's a beef burger on top, and the other one is a shrimp burger.)
- Two beef burger combos? - Two of beef and shrimp burgers...
- will be out. - Oh, okay.
I'm sorry for speaking poorly.
- That's okay. - Don't be sorry.
Don't say you're sorry.
I need someone to complete the pizza.
I'll do that.
What was I going to do?
(I'm here.)
(Oh, the pizza!)
(The forgetful younger member...)
(finished up the pizza.)
The pizza is ready too.
- I'm leaving. - See you later.
Here's the food.
(Food keeps coming out miraculously despite everything.)
(The service team is picking up the pace.)
Here's your tteokbokki.
It's very hot, so I'll hold it for you.
We need to cut this in smaller pieces.
- It's too big. - I see.
Let's ask for a knife.
- A knife? - I think we need one.
- I'll cut it with the fork. - Do you need a knife?
Shall I bring you a knife?
- Can we get scissors, please? - Sure. I'll be right back.
Thank you.
(She smoothly jumped into their conversation.)
We were supposed to give you these with the food.
- We forgot the tongs and scissors. - That's okay.
My sincere apologies.
Ye Na.
Ms. Ye Na,
I'm deeply sorry about that.
Could you please say you accept my apology?
It's okay.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(While Eun Ji saves the day thanks to the child's generosity...)
You just have to keep moving and work fast.
Making good food takes a lot of hassle.
The more hassle, the better the food. It's such a hassle.
(It's a hassle?)
Director, it'll sting.
Only a strong person like me can endure this.
Do you know what I'm afraid of?
That one day, this will all feel easy.
(It may be a hassle, but the more effort you put in...)
- Mimi. - Yes?
We're starting to run out of sauce bowls.
Sauce bowls? But I think that's...
- Oh, those sauce bowls? - Yes.
(The timing is perfect.)
- I washed these dishes. - Okay.
- Thank you so much. - She's incredible.
(A mountain of tableware arrived the moment Young Ji said it.)
She washed those at the perfect moment.
- She's incredible. Shin Gabee. - Yes.
Shin Gabee.
Can someone please help me with the potatoes?
I'll do that.
- Hello. - Oh, my.
- Gabee, thank you so much. - I washed the dishes.
It's my job.
I'm impressed. Gabee works so fast.
(Gabee, who works and moves fast,)
(restocks the self-service station.)
(It seems that she's also quick-witted.)
The bun came out great. Take a look at that.
Nice. It's amazing. It's so easy to cut.
It's so easy to cut.
That's because it's hot.
It must be hard for you. The bun is really hot.
- It's for a beef burger, right? - What do you mean?
It's for a beef burger, right?
Well, Mi Hyun, I'm grateful.
- I mean, it's for a beef burger. - Right.
What is she talking about?
(She got sentimental for a moment.)
- Seriously... - It sounded like "pretty," right?
- I thought it was "happy." - "Happy?"
- I thought she meant I was happy... - Right?
because Gabee was helping us.
Why would I ask that when it's a given?
Young Ji, where should I put this? Should I put it under here?
Yes, please. My gosh.
- That's exactly what I needed. - Is that right?
- I'll bring more. I had no idea. - She's unbelievable.
She brought me a clean food pan.
I wouldn't have been able to make any tteokbokki.
Oh, my. Unbelievable.
- Did she bring you a clean pot? - Yes, she did.
- Shin Gabee. - Thank you.
Gabee, what's the title of your new song?
- It's "Bromm, Taki." - Come again?
- "Bromm, Taki." - It sounded like "running start."
Can you say it again?
"Broom, Taki?" Oh, "Broom, Taki?"
- Yes, it's "Bromm, Taki." - "Broom, Taki."
- "Broom, Taki." - "Running Start" would be nice too.
- "Running Start." - "Broom, Taki."
(The kitchen is doing a running start.)
Please put this on your table.
(The customers are walking upstairs.)
Hello.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake. Please take a table for two.
(She told them to take a table for 2.)
(But...)
(All tables here are full.)
(There are no empty seats over there either.)
(The only table left hasn't been cleared yet.)
- No empty seats, right? - No.
- Thank you. - I'll bring them out in order.
- It'll take a while. - Okay.
(It's as if she foresaw the future.)
- Why haven't you sat down yet? - There are no tables left.
Really? A table for two?
Give me a moment, please. I'll go check.
Hello, Table Two. You ordered...
- a shrimp burger combo, right? - Yes.
You upgraded a soda to an ade, correct?
- Yes. - And...
- you ordered a margarita too, yes? - Yes.
Okay. We'll bring your food out as soon as it's ready.
- Take your time and enjoy the food. - Okay.
I'll bring you a glass of margarita.
(Now she clears the empty table.)
(She calls the customers when she's almost done.)
Please come.
- I'm very sorry. - That's okay.
We're a bit busy today.
- Did you order tteokbokki? - Yes, we did.
If you ordered tteokbokki,
I'll leave this here.
We need it to serve tteokbokki anyway.
(She nails both efficiency and service quality.)
Oh, are you done?
(The pizza master starts to communicate with the oven.)
Can I bring out anything? Is the tteokbokki almost ready?
- It'll be ready in three minutes. - The pizza is almost ready.
The pizza is coming out? Okay.
Because the dough is too thin...
- It looks messy. - Save the pretty buns.
It looks messy. I think we should make a new one.
(Reason for discarding: It's squished.)
- Take your time. No rush. - Right.
- The dough is too thin, so... - Right.
I guess we shouldn't make it too thin.
Take your time. I'll do a better job next time.
- It's okay. - You can do it.
I can do it.
Hang in there just a little longer.
(She desperately hoped for a good result, but...)
(The second pizza is...)
Please.
- Please don't do this to me. - You can do it.
We're almost there.
Oh, gosh. This is bad.
(The hardship came without any warning.)
(Reason for discarding: It's stuck to the tray.)
Hold on. This is...
Why is the dough stuck here?
- What? That's the villain. - Oh, no.
(Reason for discarding: Burnt dough)
I did it. It's all my fault.
- No. I did it. I mean, it's... - I'll do a better job tomorrow.
(As a matter of fact, hours ago...)
(The ones with dark spots...)
(Not bad?)
Is this 10mm thick?
(They were gathered 1 by 1.)
(It seems okay, so let's put it aside for now.)
(And their complacency...)
Oh, gosh. Wait. It's almost transparent.
Your table number is seven. Please take this upstairs with you.
- We got a new order. - Got it.
One beef burger,
one pizza...
One pizza...
(Another pizza!)
I think we should stop taking pizza orders.
- Let's stop taking pizza orders. - I'll let Eun Ji know.
This one looks... Is this okay?
It doesn't look acceptable, right?
Don't take any pizza orders for now, okay?
- Oh, it's sold out? - Yes.
Hello. May I take your order?
Treat yourself to a big order.
- Can we order a lot? - No.
I'm very sorry,
- but pizza is sold out. - Really?
Yes. I'm sorry.
We don't even have time to check our phones.
No, we don't. We're getting a total digital detox.
Gabee, hang in there. We only have five tables left.
I'll make you delicious tteokbokki.
It's okay. I'm happy right now.
- You're lying. - I'm being honest.
- It will be really delicious. - This is fun.
It will be really delicious.
You don't want to eat it anymore, do you?
This is fun.
You're lying.
You're a liar.
- Goodbye. - That looks delicious.
(I'm already spoken for.)
It looks delicious.
Is this one ruined?
- Yes. - Oh, it's ruined.
- You can eat it. - Then I'll eat it.
- Can you make an ade quickly? - Sure.
(Startled)
(Not even a moment of distraction is allowed.)
- We got a new order. - Okay.
- Do we sell beer here? - Of course.
(We understand how you feel, but we don't serve alcohol.)
It goes perfectly with beer.
Bravo, bravo
(As a sad melody resonates through the kitchen,)
(the pizza master finishes baking the last pizza of the day.)
Please.
(It's squished.)
Do you need any help?
I think you can just flatten it out a little bit.
- It looks okay, right? Or not? - It looks okay.
- That shouldn't be served. - It's not good?
- Is it bad? - It doesn't exactly look amazing.
- But this is the last one. - Let's give them a refund.
(It's on the house.)
- Let's make it on the house. - That'd be better.
- It's a great idea, Chef Lee. - Right.
You're really good at this.
- Eun Ji taught me this. - That's a great idea.
(She learned this when she ruined Goguryeo Ramyeon in Goheung.)
Here's the pizza you ordered.
But since it didn't come out in the right shape,
the kitchen decided to give it to you on the house.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry about that. - That's okay.
It looks fine. Guys don't care about the looks.
It's okay. Let's dig in.
(These customers are generous.)
(Even though it looks ugly, they take photos of it.)
(He cuts a small piece and puts it in his mouth.)
(Impressed)
It's like a delicious pepperoni pizza...
- A very spicy one. - with two drops of hot sauce.
(Fortunately, it seems like the pizza tastes good.)
Please insert your card.
(Crowded)
Please put this on your table.
Hello. Let me take your order. May I have your name, please?
- Gabee, could you please... - Yes?
- read out the order for them first? - Read this?
- Okay. Oh, I'm sorry. - Here's the beef... I'm sorry.
All right, let me read out the order.
One ade, one margarita,
one carrot cake,
one pizza, one tteokbokki,
and one beef burger.
- We have no pizza left. - We don't have any pizza left.
Oh, no. Why did a pizza order come in?
- Oh, right. - You should cancel the pizza order.
(However...)
- One original tteokbokki and pizza. - One pizza.
One ghost pepper pizza. This is very spicy.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Impatient Puppy forgot that it was sold out.)
- Why is there pizza? - I'll cancel it.
- We have one more order. - Okay.
Cancel pizza orders at two tables.
(Yu Jin goes upstairs to sort things out.)
I'll cancel that order.
This is for Table 12.
We're very sorry,
but the pizza is sold out.
Would it be okay if we cancelled it?
- The pizza is sold out. - I see.
- Will it be okay if we cancel it? - That can't be helped.
Wait, what's this?
What's going on here?
What is this?
(The head chef tries to decipher the orders by herself.)
(We have our first order!)
(Those who are used to hearing Yu Jin read the menu)
(With the youngest one gone)
- Beef burger and tteokbokki. - It went out.
- The original tteokbokki went out? - It went out.
- And one beef burger. - The beef burger is out.
That's correct.
Did we make any mistakes?
(Writing is in black, and paper is white.)
(Meanwhile...)
What's the matter?
Did you put basil mayonnaise instead?
- I did. - It's okay.
It's okay.
Were you there?
(Another round of chaos)
Why didn't you tell me?
Director, you betrayed me.
- At Table 12... - Margarita.
Table 12.
Eun Ji, you look very busy right now.
A margarita at Table 12?
- Margarita for Table 8. - Margarita for Table 8.
- Margarita for Table 4. - Margarita for Table 4.
- As well as Table 6. - Let's serve Table 6 later.
- One shrimp burger... - One more shrimp burger?
I got it.
(Changing the order for the cancelled table)
- We have one more shrimp burger. - What?
One more shrimp burger.
- One more order of shrimp burger. - Okay.
We have to make one more.
(The last order: 3 tteokbokki,)
(3 beef burgers, 3 shrimp burgers)
We used all the rice cakes.
We sold a lot of tteokbokki today.
Business is booming today.
(It looks like they're getting closer to the 100,000-dollar dream.)
(The floor manager who prepared a cheat sheet)
(Performing her last dance with every ounce of her soul)
(She pours out her soul.)
(She adds a spoonful of performance.)
(The margarita is ready.)
Here are your beverages.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thanks to the cheat sheet, she also finishes serving.)
Yu Jin, is the shrimp burger for the table that ordered pizza?
(The youngest who was preparing the dessert)
That's right.
One, two, three, four.
Four? Wait a minute.
One, two, three.
(3 remaining carrots)
(However, 4 carrot cakes remain to be served.)
(Unfortunately, she's short on 1.)
There's something strange about the orders.
- Yu Jin. - Yes?
- I believe we have... - Yes.
three more burgers to make.
- Isn't it 4 including... - I mean, 4.
- the shrimp burger I added earlier? - Yes.
Right.
(Remaining burger orders)
(This is what they have in mind.)
Should I go upstairs and check again?
- No, it's okay. - Is it okay?
It's okay.
- Okay. - Thank you anyway.
Gabee, you're already doing very well.
(However...)
Can I take a photo of it?
(Table 4: 1 shrimp burger combo, 1 beef burger combo)
(Table 8: 1 beef burger combo, 1 shrimp burger combo)
It's okay.
(Table 6: 1 beef burger combo, 1 shrimp burger combo)
(The actual number of burger orders)
(1 beef burger and 1 shrimp burger are missing.)
(A total of 6)
(The kitchen team has no idea either.)
Mimi, I made two beef burgers.
- Okay. - One shrimp burger.
(Yu Jin has no clue because she's busy with desserts.)
One, two. I have to make one more.
Yes, I can do it.
You can do it.
I just have to knead the dough and fry it now.
Let's go, Yu Jin.
I won't allow any more cancellations.
I can do it.
(She decides to make more carrots.)
Yu Jin, give us a shout of "ahk."
Ahk!
- All right. - Here it is.
Mimi, can I use one of the fryers?
Which one?
- Can I use this fryer? - Sure.
This or that.
It's not off, is it?
It's off.
(It's turned off.)
No one is helping me.
It's okay. You're doing very well.
Thank you for the compliment.
(Frying the carrot rice cake until crispy)
(Planting it quickly before it cools down)
- Here's your carrot cake. - Thank you.
One shrimp burger is ready.
(The burgers start coming out.)
Ta-da. Enjoy your food.
(Table 8: 1 original tteokbokki, 1 beef burger combo)
- This is the shrimp burger. - I see.
(Even the sociable part-timer)
- Yu Jin, I'll serve Table Eight. - Okay.
Erase the beef burger for Table Eight.
Number 12 and 8.
Is there anything that hasn't come out yet?
One shrimp burger is ready.
(They race toward the finish line.)
- Beef. - Shrimp burger for Table Seven.
- Table 7. - Shrimp and beef for Table 7.
- These 2 are for Table 7. - Okay.
(The part-timer goes to Table 7.)
Hello.
You're Table Seven. Is this your order?
- We never ordered it. - We got everything.
- Really? - Yes.
That's strange.
(She retreats with an awkward laugh.)
Excuse me.
Why are they making mistakes with us twice today?
Listen.
Table 7 already got 1 beef and 1 shrimp burger.
- Right? - Yes.
- It must be the one below. - Below?
- This one? - It's for this table.
Okay.
(She calls upon the power of collective intelligence again.)
One beef burger for Table Six?
- I'll also serve the shrimp burger. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
Here's your shrimp burger.
And your beef burger.
- Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Eun Ji, how are things going upstairs?
- Absolute chaos. - Absolute chaos?
Yes.
What would we have done today without Gabee?
- Exactly. - I know.
It would've been a disaster without her.
(The part-timer is cleaning up,)
(unaware of others talking about her.)
- How's the food? - We don't need...
- It's very chewy. - Really?
We'll make you more right away.
- Please wait a bit longer. - Okay.
(What's left behind after the good worker leaves)
- We must be the last customers. - That's fascinating.
- There's no one else. - You're right.
- We must be the last ones. - We should hurry.
(A table with nothing but tteokbokki)
Gabee, I'll make you some food.
- Are we really done now? - Yes.
- We're almost done. - Are we?
We're done once the original tteokbokki is served.
That's incredible. We're done.
One small original tteokbokki is ready.
(The tteokbokki they believe is their final order arrives.)
It's hot, so please don't touch it.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
(Table 6: 1 mint carrot cake)
Here's your carrot cake as well. Enjoy.
Gabee, I'll make it delicious.
Thank you. Are you making one for me too?
I'll make it the best because I'll be eating it too.
(Starting to make the staff meal that she promised)
I'll make it the best.
Hello. Did you enjoy your food?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Did you enjoy your food? - My goodness.
(Greeting the fans at the counter)
Eun Ji, you worked so hard.
You wrote the orders on yourself?
It's making me emotional.
It's going to make me cry.
(Tearing up at the orders tattooed on Eun Ji's arm)
I feel bad for her.
- Ye Seul. - Look at this.
I feel so bad about it.
(In one corner of the dining area)
(There's a table that's even more pitiful.)
You want 1 beef burger and 1 shrimp burger?
All right, let's do it.
(She makes exactly the same as the forgotten order.)
Who wants to drink this?
Who wants a pomegranate ade?
Me.
- That sounds good. - Please make one for me.
I should make it.
The last pomegranate ades.
(In a friendly atmosphere)
I'll fry the fried food again.
Of course.
I'll give you this first.
You're getting two burger combos.
Gabee, feel free to take photos of this.
Okay, I will.
- Gabee. - Yes?
Please take a break and eat.
I'll go upstairs and check.
- Did you enjoy your food? - Could you check upstairs?
Yes, please be healthy.
(Whether it's a blessing or a curse, the patrol begins.)
Gosh, it looks delicious.
Mimi, you worked so hard.
- How did you work so hard? - Gabee, you worked hard too.
(Signature menu items at Space Rice Cake)
My goodness. It looks so good.
(After working her tail off all day,)
(the part-timer takes time to capture commemorative photos.)
(The head chef finally enters the dining area.)
- Isn't it good? - Yes, it's good.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello, are you enjoying your food?
- It's so good. - Hello.
(Going around to check on the customers)
- It's delicious. - We're about to close,
so I came up to say hello.
(And...)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - How was the food?
- It was really good. - It was delicious.
- The fish... - The fish?
- Wasn't it fried well? - Yes.
I don't know who fried it. I can't wait for the burger.
It was Mimi.
- What did you say? - I can't wait for the burger.
You can't wait for the burger? What do you mean?
Which burgers did you order?
- Here it is. - I'm just curious.
I've been making burgers nonstop.
I'm just curious about your order.
- I erased what we already got. - Beef and shrimp?
(Rushing)
(She suddenly bolts back toward the kitchen.)
Freeze!
- Freeze! - What's the matter?
(Thankfully, freshly made burgers are still there.)
What's the matter?
(It's obvious that she made a mistake.)
- Wait. - What is it?
Freeze. Did you eat it already, Gabee?
- No. - I'm sorry.
- I didn't even touch it. - This isn't for you.
We need tater tots.
- Tater tots. - I thought...
I thought that it was for me.
- Which table is it? - Is it not for me?
Can I give them these pomegranate ades?
- Of course. - Three.
- Three? As an apology? - Three?
There are three people.
Wait.
Right. That wasn't right.
I'm sorry, Gabee
- I'm really sorry - I knew it.
(I'm sorry, Gabee. I'm really sorry)
Take it upstairs.
It was mine.
(Feeling awkward, she scratches the back of her neck.)
Goodness.
Goodbye.
- I'm sorry, Gabee. - Bye.
- I'm really sorry. - I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. - We asked someone this talented...
to do the dishes.
(Meanwhile, the head chef who's carrying the tray carefully)
How about some free pomegranate ade?
- That sounds great. - That'd be great.
Have some more.
Even if you already ate, have some more.
- I haven't eaten yet. - Please eat.
Or you can drink all three.
- It's really delicious. - You mean the burger?
- It looks so good. - It looks delicious.
I made the burgers too.
- I knew it. - Is it lying down? Put it up.
It's tired because it's evening. Enjoy your food.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Taking a bite of the long-awaited burger)
- The rice cake bun is good. - Yes.
It doesn't taste like rice cakes.
Which one is your favourite dish?
The burger.
It's delicious.
- Help yourself. - Okay.
- I'll make an ade for myself. - Is there anything left?
- I can have an ade, right? - Go ahead.
Of course.
- I'll make one for you. - It's okay.
- Have a seat. - Gosh.
- It's okay. - You're a customer.
Don't worry.
- There's no more ade anyway. - We feel so bad.
No, it's okay.
There was a nice atmosphere when I was taking the photos.
They looked quite good.
Gosh, this is...
- We even have two tteokbokki. - There are no buns.
(There are no buns.)
(The kitchen is in an embarrassing state.)
I feel terrible for her.
For the ade,
there's no pulp at all, which is my favourite.
Really?
I'm making it only with juice, but it's okay.
I'll be going home soon anyway.
Excuse me.
Has everything you ordered come out?
- Yes. - Gosh.
I'm glad to hear that.
Has everything you ordered come out?
- Yes. - We got everything.
- You cleaned your plate. - Yes.
- Take your time. - Okay.
- Did all your orders come out? - Yes.
Thank you.
(Back to the kitchen after checking every table)
(Current time, 8:54pm)
(Space Rice Cake)
(Closed for business)
Young Ji, could you hurry and grill some meat?
- The patties. - I'm ready to grill
- Some meat - No, it's okay.
It's okay. I don't have to eat.
You have to eat it.
- Are you making it for me? - Of course.
Really?
How can you possibly hold back from eating it?
I didn't think you were making it for me.
That's a relief.
(Starting with dishes that weren't snatched away)
Gabee, let me get you a fork.
It's okay. You have to eat pizza with your hands.
That's true.
Use this, Gabee.
- It's okay. - The dishes aren't done yet.
Gabee, use this.
Goodness.
(A bite of tteokbokki with a toddler fork)
(Humming)
Isn't it good?
It's not a place where people come...
because it's run by Earth Arcaders.
- You'd come for the food. - Right.
That's what we wanted to hear.
Wasn't today the busiest day we've had?
- It was the busiest day. - Right.
- I bet we made a lot of money. - I should check the sales.
- Could you tell us the sales... - I should take a look.
while we make the burgers?
(Gasping)
Eun Ji.
- Wait. - No way.
Are they over 1,500 dollars?
I'm not seeing it wrong, am I?
- SK Hynix? - SK Hynix?
We need to invest in SK Hynix.
Two thousand?
- Seriously? - Really?
(Sales officially passed 2,000 dollars.)
(33 beef burger combos, 17 shrimp burger combos,)
(34 original tteokbokki, 20 ghost pepper pizza...)
(Goguryeo Pizza, minus 22 dollars)
(Total sales: 2,050.6 dollars)
- Gosh, we made a lot. - Shin Gabee.
- Let's go. - Shin Gabee.
(Who am I?)
- Shin Gabee. - Let's go.
(The queen's name echoes through the kitchen.)
- Broom, Taki. - Let's go.
Broom, Taki.
(Today's MVP returns the favour with a little dance.)
- Thank you. - This is all thanks to Gabee.
Gabee, try the shrimp burger first.
(Meanwhile, a shrimp burger is made.)
Zumba.
I'll cut it for you.
- In two minutes... - Are you wearing gloves?
Yes.
It tastes best when you eat it that way.
Gabee, it's very hot.
- She's enjoying it. - It looks delicious.
(Humming)
That's an American-style reaction.
(Copying it immediately)
(Exclaiming)
- She's so kind and amazing. - An American-style reaction.
The beef burger is coming. Wait a little.
It's so good.
I love basil.
Most women like basil.
(As she likes it, she takes a big bite.)
Gosh.
(The American girl's face says it all.)
Young Ji.
That's American-style.
It's insane.
- This tastes the best. - Yes.
- I like this the best. - Is it your favourite?
- Is it number one? - Is it your favourite?
- KARINA said the same thing. - It's number one.
You're right.
- Shall I pack it up for you? - It was so good.
- Let's pack it for her. - Yes, please.
I had fun.
Time went by faster...
- than I expected. - Seriously.
Out of all of us, you talked the most.
- You were the most relaxed. - Seriously.
- You changed the entire mood. - She really did.
- You girls are so cute. - You worked so hard, Gabee.
- No. - You were a big help.
We aren't just saying it.
- You were a huge help. - Really?
- You helped out a lot. - I really enjoyed it.
I loved it, Eun Ji.
- Eun Ji... - How was it working here...
today?
I realised that I enjoy watching it.
- That's exactly it. - I like the show so much.
- Watching it is more fun. - I like the show so much...
- that I prefer to watch it. - Right.
- Gabee, I'll walk you out. - Okay.
Get going.
- It was so much fun. - Thank you.
Well done, everyone.
Congratulations on earning 2,000 dollars.
It's all thanks to you.
- It's thanks to you. - No way.
- You must be so tired. - Shin Gabee.
- Thank you. - Shin Gabee.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
I'll call you. Bye.
- Bye. - Ahk.
Ahk.
(Leaving Space Rice Cake with a sense of relief)
(A commemorative selfie in front of the restaurant)
(Just like that, our second part-timer left.)
We earned 2,000 dollars in the evening.
(Screaming)
(It's time to celebrate breaking the 2,000-dollar mark.)
(Congratulations)
(Taking a moment to fully enjoy it)
(An enthusiastic conductor and a balloon at the venue)
(Umba)
(Making sounds)
(A perfectly synchronized quartet)
(Singing)
- Dang. - Dang.
(Dang)
Let's eat delicious food tomorrow.
Our money...
(Yareu)
(Screaming with joy)
(The head chef can barely contain the joy.)
(Laughing triumphantly)
(It's hard to tell how happy she is.)
This is incredible.
We can probably buy about three Hynix shares.
The goal is to buy 4 shares and giving 1 to each of us.
This is so cute.
"Dear Earth Arcaders."
(A handwritten letter from a customer)
My child watched the show over 100 times.
- Really? - She wrote you a letter.
- My goodness. - Please read it.
Thank you so much.
- We got a letter. - Read it out loud.
"Hello, I'm "Earth Arcade" expert who watched the show..."
"from Season 1 to 3 more than 100 times."
"I'm ten-year-old Kwon Ye Na."
"Earth Arcade" expert?
"I watched it more than 100 times,"
"but it's still funny every single time."
"To me, "Earth Arcade" is the funniest show."
"It's the best variety show that I never get tired of."
"Please don't let the season ever end."
"Keep making it until I grow up."
"So girls, please don't get sick and stay healthy."
"Thank you for reading my letter all the way to the end."
She told me not to get sick.
- It hurts. - It's making me cry.
(It's making me cry.)
Mimi, are you okay?
- Are you crying? - Read this. It's so sad.
"Earth Arcade expert" is so cute.
(A heartfelt letter melts away the exhaustion.)
That's cute.
Mimi, we worked so hard today.
Young Ji, you worked very hard.
Everyone, well done today.
Okay.
- Today, - Our highest sales?
- you hit another record. - Seriously.
- Over 2,000 dollars. - We got the momentum.
(We're happy but exhausted.)
- And so... - And 50.5 dollars.
Tomorrow morning, we have to fix the faucet...
- I have to explain this. - What...
(In the middle of the dinner service)
- Gosh. - What's the matter?
Are you okay?
What happened?
Let me explain.
I went over to do the dishes.
- Or whatever it was... - What were you doing?
in the cooking process.
You know how the faucet is always set to hot water?
I had to turn it to cold. Or I would burn my hands.
- Burn your hands? - And so,
I turned it to the side like this.
Then suddenly...
- The faucet? - Yes.
- The faucet? - If I turned it sideways,
how hard could I have possibly turned it?
It ended up like this.
My first thought was,
"Someone must have broken it earlier."
The point is, even if you want to prep tonight,
you can't because of the faucet.
- So you wanted to share good news. - To wash...
You won't be able to wash anything.
So you should go home and recharge tonight.
- Take a rest tonight. - We need to rest.
And...
- come in tomorrow at 9:30am. - At 9:30am?
- How about that? - Okay.
Let's focus on our victory...
- of earning 2,050 dollars. - Heart.
Heart.
Honesty, humility, ahk.
(Congratulating themselves again)
- Honesty, humility, ahk. - Honesty, humility, ahk.
Please say it out loud.
- Give us one little word. - She got me.
- I was lip-syncing. - Give us one little word.
- Honesty, humility, ahk. - Honesty, humility, ahk.
(She got caught red-handed.)
- Honesty, humility, ahk. - I'm so glad.
It's over. Please go home.
Please.
Director, please save me.
- Get up. - I'm begging you.
Please get up.
How many times are you going to lie down here?
The floor is cold. Your mouth will freeze.
It'll be refreshing again.
Goodbye.
Gosh, my feet.
We get off work and come in very regularly.
- Is this deja vu? - Seriously.
(They go home completely beat yet again today.)
Today was really exhausting.
- Out of all the seasons... - "Out of all?"
This is the only season which we didn't film a challenge.
- We didn't even dance. - We did dance a few times.
I have no new pictures of us in my phone gallery.
- I'm falling over. - Seriously.
My body is slowly folding.
But I think I'm cut out for this.
- It's fun. As I said... - Yes.
- It's nice. - It's tiring but fun.
It's so tiring that I'm enjoying it.
- Really? - So it got rid of my evil side.
- You've reached enlightenment. - Evil, go away
(Laughing)
- And I think I really love them. - The people?
- Cooking? - No, the three of you.
- Oh, my gosh, I'm so touched. - I'm dead serious.
- I really love you guys. - It's love.
I want to kiss you passionately.
One after another.
- I don't fancy such a woman. - You don't?
- Thank you for driving, Yu Jin. - Thank you.
(Anyway, she means she gets her energy from the members.)
- I want to check if she's sleeping. - Sexy and professional.
I didn't understand when people said your evil side would come out.
You feel it, don't you?
- Yu Jin was really busy today. - Yes, your evil side comes out...
when you're busy.
- As I saw her work, - You're right.
I was amazed that she still pulled it off.
Everyone worked so hard today.
- Everyone had it rough today. - But it's fun, right?
I feel love...
Who are you? This is her evil speaking too.
- It's tough but fun, right? - Get out.
No. There were fun moments here and there.
That's why.
If you're okay with it, then I'm glad.
- Yes. - Actually, this restaurant...
isn't focused on tteokbokki.
So I thought we'd cut down on tteokbokki slowly...
as we got used to the new menus.
Or what about keeping a limit to the amount of servings...
- for tteokbokki? - It's so...
No, let's just sell five pizzas.
But the pizzas impact the sales greatly.
- The most, actually. - It's crazy.
We hit 2,000 dollars after we started selling them.
- Pizzas are insane. - But...
Or cut down on burgers?
(Agenda 1. Reducing menus)
- Margarita. Let's cut down on it. - Because...
- Yes, let's get rid of margarita. - I need Eun Ji.
My heart breaks when you come down late.
- Exactly. I feel anxious too. - My heart sinks.
- We can get rid of margarita. - I need you.
(Margarita is out.)
Honestly, if you're fine with it, Young Ji,
I think it's time to let tteokbokki go.
- Yes, let's remove tteokbokki. - Let's remove tteokbokki.
Then I don't need to serve tongs and scissors?
That's right.
You don't need to serve tongs and scissors,
nor do you need to serve the mitts.
(Original tteokbokki is out.)
- I can do that. - I think Mimi needs...
- a dish of her own too. - That's right.
- You're in the kitchen team. - Tacos.
(Agenda 2. Mimi's new menu)
- Let's add your new menu. - That's right.
- Okay, I'm ready. - You can do it.
- Come at me! - Mimi.
(What is it?)
(Thus, they were thinking about the new menu for Mimi.)
But if you do the new menu tomorrow,
you could do tacos.
- Tacos? - Gosh, I just said it.
Darn it.
(Self spoiler)
(Are you serious?)
Delete.
(Memory deleted)
A cooking variety show makes the producer lose her mind too.
Is it rice cake too?
Lay out rice crackers...
We were going to put some things on rice crackers.
I love that.
(Well, since it's been revealed anyway,)
(tomorrow's new menu using crispy rice crackers)
(New menu, rice cracker taco)
(Rice cracker has been to Mexico to study.)
(Space Rice Cake's finger food menu, rice cracker taco)
If the new dish is taco, it really suits Mimi.
Mimi, start tomorrow right away.
Yes. Hand over the shrimp burger to me.
- You should do it. - I will.
What you were doing...
- Just do pizza and taco. - Yes.
Tomorrow, we'll remove tteokbokki...
and go with shrimp burger, beef burger, and taco.
Let's go Italian and Mexican tomorrow.
Sounds good.
You're in charge of similar food. Taco and lasagna.
- I... - Pasta.
Mexico.
- Spain. - Style your hair like this again.
- Mexico... - It suits you.
"Coco" vibe.
(New dish, rice cracker taco, is out!)
Another day of business
(Eun Ji is styling herself.)
I don't think this is right.
You look so cute.
It's "I'm Sorry, I Love You" vibe.
Redoing it? It is cute, though.
(Candidate 2: Rabbit hat again)
(Candidate 3: 1990s retro)
Don't I look like someone from the 1990s?
Now that you say it, you do look like one.
What can I do not to go?
I'll drive your car and send you to your homes.
- My gosh. - Sounds good. Let's go to my house.
Drop Eun Ji off first.
- The nearest house. - Her house is so close.
It's literally so close.
(The reality feels even harsher because her house is so close.)
Producer. You know, the blue "Earth Arcade" cap.
Do you have a big one? I have a big head.
- This one? - Yes.
- It's free size. - Oh, dear.
- Loosen the back. - You can loosen it.
I loosened it all the way, and it was still small.
- No way. - I'm serious.
(She loosens it all the way and tries wearing it.)
- You're checking with this. - I didn't check.
(Odd)
This part...
- I should do this and bring it. - Yes.
(Copying Young Ji, Yu Jin wears a bandana too.)
I'm copying you.
- Thank you. - That looks cute.
- You should wear them together. - Hip hop kids?
- This... Let's go. - Let's go.
(Ryang Hyun Ryang Ha are ready to go.)
The weather is fantastic.
- Every single day. - Exactly.
(Space Rice Cake...)
(Even before the members have arrived)
They must prepare everything here.
(There's someone in the kitchen.)
A blender.
(An unknown man is already at work.)
Do they deep-fry the patties?
(While waiting for the members,)
(he is exploring thoroughly.)
(Strong arms trained from working on a ranch)
It'll be nice to have more green.
(His hands look like they'd smell of taco.)
(He even has cooking skills suitable for running a cafeteria.)
(Today's part-timer has charms which pop like popcorn.)
It's nice.
I'm done. I just need to wait for them to come.
(Meanwhile, the members have no clue about him.)
- Tired and ill Earth Arcaders - Ill
- We're doing business today too - We
There's rice cake outside again.
(They arrive in the dark.)
(They climb up the stairs as usual.)
I forgot to get coffee.
- The bottom one... - Hold on.
(They take the rice cakes and get to work as usual.)
(One different thing...)
- Welcome. - We're here.
Goodness.
(A silhouette in the kitchen)
- We're at the restaurant. - We're here.
(They walk past the kitchen without suspecting anything.)
- Let's put it down here. - This is crazy.
(The back of the man who's waiting for them)
(The second team enters without a suspicion too.)
Be careful.
(The Earth Arcaders can't see what's right under their noses.)
Done.
Goodness.
Hello... Gosh! Kyung Soo.
(Surprise.)
Hello.
- Kyung Soo. - Hello, Young Ji.
(She who runs away as soon as she sees him)
- When did you come? - Hello.
(She who acts awkward)
- You should greet him. - Hello.
- Hello. - Kyung Soo.
Why does everyone look so tired?
We're so tired. It's so hard.
You sure look tired.
(That's why I'm here to help.)
Kyung Soo is here, guys.
(Great at acting)
(Great at variety shows)
(Great at singing)
(An all-rounder part-timer, Doh Kyung Soo)
Kyung Soo.
We've had two part-timers so far.
You're the first one who arrived before the shop opened.
They told me to come before it opened.
- And he... - You're the first.
- isn't just any part-timer. - He's experienced.
(2 years of experience as the director of KKPP Food)
- Today... - Really? Yes.
- The new menu... - Taco?
- Taco. - is taco. So...
we invited the expert...
(Last July, the director went to Mexico to explore.)
- who learned it from Mexico. - Hurrah.
(A very reliable part-timer who studied overseas)
Taco.
(Welcome.)
- Thank you in advance. - Thank you in advance.
- Doh Kyung Soo. - Let's get started quickly.
Kyung Soo, can we just teach you one thing first?
- What is it? - Honesty, humility.
(Embarrassed)
- We... - "Honesty, humility?"
We have the restaurant's signature...
- cheer. - Be honest and humble?
- No. Honesty, humility. - Humility.
- Ahk. - Ahk.
"Ache?"
- It means "brother" in Abu Dhabi. - Brother.
(She usually has no problem with it, but she's feeling very shy today.)
Please do it with us.
(They'll all say it together.)
- Honesty, humility, - Honesty, humility,
- ahk. - ahk.
- Guys, wait. - Let's do it again.
How will you do business if you're acting so shy?
- I feel so awkward. - Why are you acting so shy?
- This is... - Why...
only my second time seeing him.
He has so many years above mine in terms of tenure.
Oh, to you guys...
- Many years... - Yes, many years.
- Many years. I see. - I guess that's how they feel.
When did you debut?
- In 2012. - In 2012.
- Oh, in 2015. - In 2015.
- In 2019. - In 2019.
- In 2018. - In 2018.
Yu Jin, have you never met Kyung Soo before?
When he was in the most recent MMA.
- Right. We passed by, - In an award show.
- and that was it. - We passed by each other.
- In an award show. - I...
Guys, why are you acting so shy?
Do something about them.
- Kyung Soo, what should we do? - It's my first time seeing him.
- What should we do? - It's my first time.
- We need to learn from him now. - Right.
He is your senior,
- but he's a senior in cooking too, - That's right.
- so learn from him. - I need to learn.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
(They'll get closer slowly as they prepare.)
- Let's do this. - Wash your hands.
(Washing hands before preparing)
I'm glad you're here, Kyung Soo. You're reliable.
Will you be here until the end?
- I'm here the whole day. - "Until the end."
- Until the end? - Until dinner?
That's what they told me.
Kyung Soo has never served before.
(He has 0 year of experience in serving.)
- So... - I was always in the kitchen.
- Then we should ask you to serve. - So...
the service team will teach him how to serve.
- Nice. - Nice.
I'll first teach Mimi how to make the taco.
- Okay. - Let's gather again for the prep.
- I got it. - We can disperse for now.
He's charismatic.
- Let's go. - He's efficient.
(Current time, 9:58am)
Guys, let's make the dough. How do I do it?
Just roll out the dough, and I'll grill it.
- Tap it with your hand. - Just simply do it.
Tap it.
(Yu Jin prepares carrot rice cakes.)
Young Ji, let's get 250g right.
Let's try to find the right weight for 250g.
Once you get the hang of it, it'll be easy.
Slightly more than a fistful?
Slightly more than a fistful.
(Getting the feel of the right amount of rice cake)
I think about this much.
Did you get the feeling?
- Yes, it's 334g. - Good job, Young Ji.
(She's nowhere close.)
(It's the floor manager Eun Ji's turn.)
It's 258g, Young Ji!
- I can use this. It's just 8g over. - Perfect.
It's perfect. You're good.
(This time)
(She seems to have gotten the hang of it and tries again.)
(Surprised)
That's exact.
(She gets exactly 250g this time.)
- Get the feeling. - You got the feeling.
(Meanwhile, the head chef...)
It's 258g. This is fine.
Darn it.
(All she can do is sigh.)
Put this on your gloves.
(She's high-maintenance.)
Seriously.
(Meanwhile, Mimi, the taco disciple...)
I'm learning how to make taco.
- Let's start. - Is "taco" Spanish?
Isn't it English?
- Is "taco" Spanish? - Yes.
- I don't know about that. - I see.
- Since you're a taco expert. - It's Mexican food, right?
- Mexican. - It's Mexican food.
Mexico speaks Spanish, right?
(Another question)
- So what we're going to do is... - Yes.
(First, Mexican stir-fried beef)
- Minced meat. - Bring it over.
Bring it over.
When it's heated, add three scoops.
(Add minced meat into the heated wok.)
- One tablespoon. Add this much. - Okay.
One tablespoon.
(Mexican stir-fried beef: Add 1 cup of minced chuck eye roll,)
(salt, pepper, and minced garlic and stir-fry them.)
- What we're going to do now... - Yes.
Let's make the taco sauce over here.
(Next, making the taco sauce!)
Mix them here in the ratio of 1 to 1 to 1.
This...
Open it like this and use a spoon.
(You can open the lid and scoop it up using a spoon.)
Okay? You can do it.
(Embarrassed)
(Taco sauce made after opening the lid)
(Add coriander powder to cumin powder...)
(and smoked paprika powder to add the local flavour.)
Teacher, do I mix them?
I mix them all, right?
(Stepping up to her)
How many spoonfuls did you add?
(Clearing her throat)
Three spoons.
- You did that, right? - Yes.
- Three spoons of this too. - Okay.
(She's walking on eggshells even more than usual.)
(The taco sauce completed under strict supervision)
Half a spoonful.
(It's added to stir-fried beef.)
It's just half a spoonful, but...
- not this kind of half. - Okay.
Just this much.
- A small half spoonful. - Okay, a small half spoonful.
Got it? Stir-fry it now.
Okay.
(It feels like he's an instructor, not a part-timer.)
- This is rice cake. - Injeolmi.
(While the taco instructor has left his post...)
I think he's more on the strict side.
(As soon as he leaves, she shares her honest thoughts.)
Honestly, I can't remember much.
(Her anxiety has clouded her mind.)
(Walking up to her again!)
- How is it, sir? - I think it's good.
(She may have gotten confused, but it looks rather appetizing!)
If you've stir-fried it this much, turn off the gas.
Turn off the gas.
(Second: Tomato salsa)
- Now, this is how you cut tomatoes. - Yes.
- Follow me. - Okay.
First, cut it into half.
Cut it into half.
- Goodness. No. - Hold on.
- Like this... - Yes.
(I can do it like this.)
(Is there any issue?)
- This is what we'll do. - I'm here.
(The cutting lesson continues.)
From the inside, cut it into long pieces.
(After cutting it into long pieces, chop it.)
Like paprika.
Excuse me.
You can put it here.
My heart fluttered.
- My heart fluttered just now. - This...
I thought...
I was getting in his way of work,
so I was going to move it away.
He was like, "You can put it here."
Pressing it down with a bit of pressure...
using his hand felt sexy.
(He fails to hold back his laughter.)
Hey, Sexy Doh!
I'm not used to this.
That was so heart-fluttering.
The kitchen looks pink now.
He's good at his job, and that makes him look so sexy.
(Eun Ji has wormed her way into the director's heart.)
(Next, cutting onions)
- This is how you cut it. - Yes.
- Onions. - Onions.
- Follow me. - Okay.
(They watch the instructor's demonstration.)
From here, cut it small.
(Yu Jin follows rather well.)
Is this enough?
Yes, looks good.
You're good at giving compliments, Director.
- If you don't do well, - Why is he a director?
you're in for trouble.
Understood, Director.
- I will do well, Director. - Okay.
- I'll do my best. - Good luck.
Good luck.
- The remaining part at the end. - Yes.
- Flip it forward. - Forward.
And this...
Forward!
- Backward! - Backward.
- Sideways. - Sideways.
Okay.
(Back to her position)
- You've figured out the kitchen. - Yes.
No.
(Chasing him around all day long)
- Director. - Yes.
Have some water.
(All she knows about is love.)
Thank you.
What are your positions?
She's the head chef.
You're the director, she's the sous chef,
and we're actually servers.
- Servers? - Yes.
(Laughing)
(Director Doh finds her a bit overwhelming.)
(And Yu Jin is still struggling with the onion.)
Cut.
(Very slow)
You can't have this.
- Oh, this. - Imagine we go to a restaurant...
and we're served this.
- Eun Ji. - How would you feel?
(A big onion piece)
Lucky.
Because it's delicious?
(It's a big piece of onion. How lucky!)
They gave me a big portion. Lucky.
Please cut it.
Director, you're really good at cutting.
Won't you do more?
(Director's cutting starts now.)
(Fancy knife skills)
(Fancy face is a plus.)
(The ingredients prepared by the director)
(Tomato salsa: Mix tomatoes, onions, lime juice and zest,)
(olive oil, minced jalapeno, minced coriander,)
(salt, pepper, and sugar)
- Sprinkle it? - One more.
Shouldn't we put a lot of meat?
- I think this is enough. - Okay.
- And on top of it, - On top of it.
add the salsa.
(Next, put tomato salsa.)
For ten, how many spoonfuls?
- Four. - That's right.
- Just... - Wing it.
Wing it.
(Savoury sour cream)
It looks so delicious.
- Drizzle it like this. - Okay.
- Watch your hands for this. - Okay.
- Grind it this much. - Okay.
(Coriander pesto: Blend coriander, garlic, pine nuts,)
(parmigiano cheese, pecorino cheese, olive oil, salt, and pepper)
This...
(Coriander pesto to be served in a separate saucer...)
(so they can choose to have it)
It looks good.
(Complete)
The coriander pesto tastes amazing.
It's so delicious.
(Taco party in his mouth)
(Very satisfied)
(Eun Ji takes a big bite too.)
Is it good?
It's good.
I love coriander, you see.
(The other members try a bite too.)
Bite it.
(Surprised)
Yu Jin doesn't like coriander, but she says it's delicious.
- It's delicious. - It's so good, Director.
Squeeze it? Okay.
(Since they've tasted it...)
What should we name the taco?
Coriander pesto taco.
- Coriander pesto taco. - Let's make something cool.
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro...
- Something cool. - taco.
I like uno, dos, tres, taco.
Uno, dos, tres, taco.
(New menu: Uno, dos, tres, taco!)
(Eun Ji practices making yuzu ade, taco's partner.)
(First, add a generous amount of yuzu marmalade.)
(Add ice to make it cold.)
(Fill it up with refreshing carbonated water.)
(Mix it thoroughly.)
Why don't we use apple mint instead of rosemary...
for yuzu ade?
(And the completed ade...)
(One step behind you)
(Always)
(I was there)
(Singing a serenade one step to his side)
- Director. - Yes.
I'd like to add yuzu ade to the menu today.
- Can you try it? - You made it?
Yes.
- Yuzu ade. - Yes.
(Looking forward to his comment)
(Director tries the yuzu ade.)
This is it.
- It's good. - Is it?
It's so good.
Thank you.
(Yuzu ade is added to the menu.)
(Preparing the rest of the dishes)
(Put your weight on it)
(They sing and prepare energetically.)
I can do it.
Kyung Soo, you were born in the earlier months of 1992, right?
- In the earlier months of 1993. - In 1993.
Then how should we go about it?
I was born in early 1993.
You were born in early 1992, right?
Then you're older than me.
- I'm older than you. - Yes.
- You might be a year apart. - Come on, Eun Ji.
(Hating it)
- What's up with you? - That was a long buildup.
It was a long buildup.
It took forever...
- I know. - to hear what she wanted.
"You're older than me."
I like that.
She's older than me.
Gosh. I can't stop smiling.
Eun Ji.
(Embarrassed by Eun Ji's brazenness)
(You're mine)
(Reached fatal level of excitement)
Good luck.
Director Doh told me, "Good luck."
(Jumping high, almost reaching the sky)
(She's embarrassing for some reason.)
Good luck, Director Doh.
Let's do this.
- I need to pan-fry the dough. - Do it.
- I'll do it, Young Ji. - We turn the heat off, right?
Thanks.
Kyung Soo, you can roll it until you reach the second line.
(Thanks to him, Young Ji starts pan-frying the dough.)
(He rolls out the dough firmly.)
- When the rice cake hardens, - I know.
- it's hard to roll it out. - That's right.
- We should've used plastic wrap. - Exactly.
(He's decided to stretch the dough by hand.)
Young Ji, is this big enough?
Yes. That's it.
Are we cooking it now?
(It goes right on the pan after getting confirmed.)
Thank you.
Plastic wrap.
(He gets straight to work on the next one.)
Nice.
(Staring)
Do you want it, Young Ji?
- What? - Where's the pan?
- What? I don't. - I'm ready.
- Please wait. - It's ready.
Please hold on.
We don't have to use a rolling pin to stretch the dough.
You're frustrated, aren't you?
No.
We can stretch it by hand and finish it with a rolling pin.
What? Do you need it now?
(Waiting for the head chef's call)
(The head chef is intimidated by him.)
Right?
(Accident)
(The director's push led to a disaster.)
(Reading the room)
(Disposing it secretly)
Nobody noticed it.
We made 12 pieces of dough, though.
(When the head chef's reputation was almost tarnished...)
It's okay. Breathe.
Do you need my help? Anything?
- I need a favour. - What is it?
Cut it in half.
It's very hard, and the bun is super hot.
Wear the gloves.
It works better with a cold, small knife.
With a cold one.
(Slicing it horizontally)
It's difficult to... No.
- Slice it this way. - This way.
- This way. - Like sashimi.
- It's hot. - I don't need a knife for it.
It isn't easy, is it?
(The director can also make mistakes sometimes.)
It's all right, Director.
Use the knife you feel comfortable with.
Yes. Everyone has their own style that they're comfortable with.
(He tries to fix it by hand.)
(Destroyed)
I messed one up, Young Ji. Sorry.
- It's totally fine. - It's okay.
(This rice cake bun can't be saved.)
- You can pay for it. - Okay.
- It's 13.9 dollars. - It's 13.9 dollars.
You can pay 13.9 dollars.
(His pay got deducted before he even gets it.)
- He ruined one. - He messed it up.
How long do we have before opening?
- How long do we have? - It's one minute before opening.
- We have 1 minute. - We have 1 minute.
We are...
open.
Open.
We're open now.
- Gosh. - Go to the counter, Kyung Soo.
Okay.
(The part-timer gets ready to greet the customers.)
(Writing down notes not to make mistakes)
(Yu Jin is finishing up the prep.)
(Reliable)
- I'll put it here for now. - Yes. I'll take these away soon.
Okay.
- Will you slice open more buns? - Yes.
- Give them to me. - When you get busy,
- Give them to me now. - I can't ask you to do it.
By the way, why are we slicing the buns...
when the customers haven't even arrived?
It's because our positions shifted quite a bit today.
- You're nervous. - Yes.
(There are some changes in kitchen assignments today.)
(Due to the launch of the taco business,)
(Chef Mimi is in charge of the taco station.)
(And Young Ji is in charge of the burger station.)
(Will the kitchen team make it despite the role changes?)
Let's do this.
- Honesty. - Humility.
- Ahk. - Ahk.
- Ahkkung? - Ahk.
Louder. Honesty.
- Humility. - Hey. We have customers.
Okay.
(Startled)
Welcome. Hello.
Hello. Hi.
What's your name?
(He welcomes the first customer calmly.)
It's Kim Hyeon Ju.
- Kim Hyeon Ju. - Hello. I love you...
as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Why don't you go to the website? Right. Hyeon Ju. You did it already.
You can choose from the menu.
We'll get the beef taco, pizza, and cake.
- As for the drink... - As for the drink,
it's included in the combo.
Then we'll get this one.
You can change it to an ade if you want.
Okay.
- Will it be yuzu or pomegranate? - Will it be yuzu or pomegranate?
- What will it be between the two? - We'll get a soda.
A soda?
- You won't change it to an ade. - No.
Kyung Soo is amazing.
I said, "Will it be yuzu or pomegranate?"
And I broke into a laugh.
"Will it be yuzu or pomegranate?"
"Which one do you want?" He changed it like that.
What's important for us is how to handle the situation.
- He's good at handling situations. - Handling a situation.
He handles the situation perfectly.
I'll give you number one.
Cake, pizza,
beef burger, and shrimp burger. One of each.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Okay. What did you say?)
(The dishes they ordered were...)
(beef burger combo, rice cracker taco,)
(ghost pepper pizza, and mint carrot cake.)
(That was the order.)
(But the order the part-timer delivered were...)
(mint carrot cake, ghost pepper pizza,)
(beef burger combo...)
(And the shrimp burger, not the taco with rice cracker?)
(Order Status: Rice cracker taco, forgotten)
(Shrimp burger, created)
It's for Table One.
Okay.
It's 1 shrimp burger and 1 beef burger.
(She hears about the shrimp from all over the place.)
- Come here, Kyung Soo. - Okay.
Did you type in all of the orders they made?
Yes.
- One pizza. - A pizza, a cake, and a drink.
- What are they drinking? - They'll get a Coke.
They'll get a Coke.
- Is the shrimp order in there? - The shrimp?
They didn't order the shrimp burger. They ordered beef and...
Beef and...
You said a shrimp burger.
- What are you... - I made a mistake. Sorry.
- Gosh. It's okay. - It's all right.
- It's okay. - It was a beef burger.
Okay.
- No shrimp burger. - And a ghost pepper pizza?
- The shrimp burger isn't it. - And a ghost pepper pizza.
(Laughing)
- It's okay. - It's all right.
- I'm sorry. - Don't be.
They didn't order the shrimp burger, right?
- That's right. They didn't. - Got it.
- Let me double-check. - Okay. He went to double-check.
(Rushing over)
I'm sorry,
- but you didn't order the shrimp. - No.
- It was a beef burger, right? Okay. - Yes.
(Embarrassed)
There's no order for a shrimp burger.
(From shrimp burger to pizza,)
(Mimi changes her task.)
(The part-timer catches his breath and looks for things to do.)
When are you going to make the taco?
We'll make it once we get the order.
We didn't get an order for the taco, did we?
We have an order for the taco.
Do we have an order for it?
Do we have an order for the taco?
We don't have an order for it.
Didn't they order tacos?
- They didn't. - I didn't put it in the order.
Did they order it?
- I'll go and ask them. - Seriously. What's up with you?
- He's... - Director Doh.
What's gotten into him?
(Figuring out the situation)
(Rushing for the 2nd time)
- Sorry, did you order a taco? - Yes.
Right? I'm sorry.
Would you give me the card you paid with?
I'll make the payment again and bring it back to you. Sorry.
- I'm the worst. - That one.
- Did they order the taco? - They ordered the taco.
I'll run the card again.
The taco was on the receipt, though.
- Please make the taco. - It's on here, isn't it?
(It's on the receipt.)
One of them and...
- Is that taco? - Yes. The rice cracker taco.
You did it right.
- I did it right, didn't I? - Yes.
(She can't believe how hectic he is.)
He's out of it today.
(They identified the uno, dos, tres, taco!)
(Rushing over again)
- The order was correct. Thanks. - Thank you.
I think this is crazy.
(This is crazy in a positive way.)
I didn't call it out.
The uno, dos, tres, taco is the taco.
I know.
- I'm sorry. - Hurry.
Chef.
- You can't do this later on. - I got it.
We'll all get sick.
I've never worked in a hall... What's it called?
I've never taken an order before.
It almost killed me.
Right. I should've put you in the kitchen.
- I feel more comfortable cooking. - You do.
(The part-timer has a distinct specialty.)
Okay. Please go upstairs.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- We have an order. - Okay.
A beef burger, a shrimp burger,
a pizza, and a taco.
- Go, Mi Hyun. - Okay.
Go.
(She makes the new dish, the rice cracker taco.)
(Stir-fry minced garlic and ground meat thoroughly.)
I'm halving the recipe.
One spoon.
(Sprinkling Director Doh's taco seasoning)
(Season it with salt and pepper.)
(After stir-frying it with quick flicks of her wrist,)
(the Mexican grilled beef is ready.)
(She tastes it.)
It's so good.
(In the meantime,)
(the head chef places a new patty,)
(and grabs the well-cooked one...)
(to assemble the beef burger quickly.)
- Yu Jin. - Yes?
What do you think of the speed of the burger-making?
Gosh. I find it sexy.
- The beef burger for Table One. - Okay, Chef.
It'll be great...
if the burger is served with the rice cracker taco.
- The taco? Give me a second. - Okay.
Rice cracker taco? Okay.
- It'll take some time, Eun Ji. - Okay.
Six.
And seven.
I was told to add lots of stir-fried beef.
One scoop.
(Sour cream)
Parmigiano.
(Finishing it with Parmigiano...)
(and red pepper flakes)
Good.
(With the coriander pesto,)
(the first rice cracker taco is ready.)
Okay. Here we go. Here's the rice cracker taco.
- Gosh. - Look at that.
- Mimi. You did a great job. - Yes. Nice.
- Please wait. Hold the taco. - What?
She forgot to put avocado.
(Don't forget the avocado.)
It looks abundant now.
(It looks more delicious with the avocado.)
- I'll bring them upstairs. - Yes, Chef.
Thank you.
- Go ahead, Director Doh. - Okay.
Here's your order.
(They're meeting for the 4th time when he's serving for the 1st time.)
This is the rice cracker taco.
This is coriander... Well...
It's a sauce made with coriander.
If you can't eat coriander,
you probably can't have it.
- Please enjoy. - Thanks.
(His first serving was complete while worrying about their tastes.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Welcome. - Please get their orders.
- We'll get one taco. - Okay.
(Now, he takes orders like a pro.)
And one carrot cake.
- A taco and a shrimp burger. - Okay.
(Order Status: 2 tacos, pizza, 2 carrot cakes,)
(yuzu ade, pomegranate ade)
Do I put yuzu in here?
Yes. You use these for both ades.
(The part-timer makes the ades this time.)
(The first order of the yuzu ade)
(First, put a generous amount of the yuzu marmalade.)
Here's the sparkling water.
(Add cold ice and sparkling water.)
(Give it a nice stir.)
(Decorate it with apple mint.)
Here's the ade.
(The part-timer's first ade is ready.)
- This is hot. - Okay.
- The dough size is perfect today. - The pizza is looking great.
- Right? The dough's nice. - Yes. It's perfect.
(The pizza quality improves by the day.)
I need someone. Someone needs to come with me.
- I'll go with you. - Okay.
Here's your pizza. It's spicy, so be careful.
This is the beef burger, and this is the shrimp. Enjoy.
- Yes. Thank you. - Thank you.
(Meanwhile in the kitchen...)
Because tteokbokki abandoned me,
I'm the queen of burgers today.
- Mimi, is it 170°C? - It's 170°C. This?
- Yes. It has to be 170°C. - It's 300°C.
- What? Is it 300°C? - It can't be 300°C, can it?
Right. It's 171°C.
(A rocky start)
Here I go. My first shrimp patty.
(The queen's first shrimp patty)
What now?
(While the patty fries,)
(she sets up the burger structure.)
- Mi Hyun. - Yes?
Please check I'm doing okay after serving that.
- Isn't it okay? - It's okay.
Nice.
(The shrimp patty is nice and golden.)
It'll be great to serve the taco with the shrimp burger.
- It's coming. - Yes. It's almost ready.
The shrimp burger is ready.
Here's the shrimp burger.
(Mimi, Young Ji's frying teacher,)
(completes a rice cracker taco without missing anything.)
- Here's another taco. - Okay.
- Here's your order. - That was quick.
- This is the rice cracker taco. - Okay.
- We'll serve the burger too. - Thank you.
Here are your pizza and taco.
I'll give you the pizza first.
- Do you have a straw? - Do you need a straw?
- Do you need one more straw? - Yes.
Okay.
(Eun Ji grabs the straw.)
Kyung Soo, here's the straw for Table Two.
We're in perfect sync. This feels great.
This is so satisfying.
- Why? - We're a perfect duo.
I gave him the straw. He gave me the tray.
And we went our separate ways.
Look at this, everyone. Because we're in sync,
we served Table 2 and Table 3 at once.
Nice.
We're on fire today.
(Order Status: All dishes are cleared.)
(The customers try the rice cracker taco.)
- It's good. - This is a great idea.
This taco shell is interesting.
Do you like it?
Yes, the taco shell is a bit...
- like crackers. - Yes.
It tastes like the rice crackers for kids.
(While the customers enjoy the food...)
Too much rice cake in a burger. A beef burger combo.
You'll switch your drink to a pomegranate ade.
A shrimp burger and...
They'll order a beef burger. Right, Mimi?
I think so.
- I'll fry the patty. - I'll sneak a peek.
Did he say, "I'll sneak a peek?"
He's good.
(Literally, he approaches...)
(and stares at it.)
A taco and a shrimp burger.
- Here's your receipt. - Hello.
(Sneaking another peek)
- A taco, a shrimp, and a beef. - I'll make a taco.
We got the order for the beef burger too.
(The part-timer's spying skill is incredible.)
Kyung Soo.
If you can make the ade,
- I'll do the dishes. - Okay.
(Dividing the tasks for efficiency)
(Yu Jin and Young Ji also split up the burger-making duties.)
- Gosh. You're good. - Gosh.
- Goodness. We're doing great today. - We're doing great.
We are so relaxed
It's so much easier with tteokbokki off the menu.
We're a real fast-food joint now.
We have to revive tteokbokki.
(They're more than relaxed. They're bored.)
I really have nothing to do.
- Don't say that. - I have nothing to do.
I'll put the taco here, Eun Ji.
Thanks. I love the taco station over here.
- Eun Ji. - Yes?
You want to serve the shrimp burger and the beef burger together.
You're so fast. You're the best.
- Here are the burgers. - Gosh. You're fast.
- Of course, I'm fast. - Thank you.
Here's your order.
(They served the dishes that are ready right away.)
- Here's your food. - Okay. Thanks.
How do you like the taco?
- It's good. - It's delicious.
Do you like it? Thanks.
Producer Ye Seul underestimated us.
I told you to stop saying that.
(It goes without saying that they're not busy.)
We have a part-timer today.
- We have to show how busy we get. - Is it too easy for him?
Usually, we're much busier than this.
- We get really busy. - We get super busy.
- This is crazy. - You're relaxed.
We should let him have some over here.
Have some ice water.
- Thanks. - Come on.
No. I prepare it myself.
Come on, Kyung Soo.
Why are you so sweet?
- You're driving me crazy. - Director Doh.
Drink some, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
Director Doh prepared it for us. Gosh. What do we do with him?
I'll share with Young Ji.
- You're so sweet. - Someone was eating it, right?
(The kitchen team meets secretly.)
- Good job. - Yesterday's sales must be higher.
- Right? - I think so too. We need to...
We need to put tteokbokki back on the menu.
- Our sales are decreasing. - Our sales are dropping.
- Tteokbokki is a sweet deal. - We need it back on the menu.
She wants to suffer.
- Our sales are decreasing. - Our sales are dropping.
Let's put everything on the menu tomorrow.
If you want to serve everything,
Kyung Soo has to come back to serve tables.
- Come back tomorrow. - He can come again.
I fly overseas tomorrow.
- To Macau. - What time?
Tomorrow...
- Are you flying out in the evening? - I think it's in the morning.
- Really. - He's lying.
- I'm serious. - Hey, Kyung Soo.
- Give me your phone. - Let's check his flight ticket.
- Are you telling the truth? - I am.
- Who's coming tomorrow, then? - Wait a second.
- Welcome. Hello. - Hello.
(The customers come in to save him.)
Welcome.
I love you as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Hello.
Where are you going, Kyung Soo? Take the orders.
We took a half day off for this.
Did you? Because it's a weekday? Thank you.
Thank you.
(Singing "Catch Catch" with the customer...)
(who took a half day off)
You don't usually get the receipt, but you got it...
- because it was from him. - You're right.
Before you go, let us do this.
I love you as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Two, three.
- Please enjoy. - You can go upstairs now.
They ordered one of each.
- Call them out for us. - Okay.
A cake, a pizza,
a taco, a shrimp burger, and a beef burger.
- Answer me. - Okay.
- Seriously. - He's scary.
- You have to respond. - You have to make a cake.
Okay.
It's 130°C. It's turned off.
Why is this so arrogant?
- I told you. - I hate it.
Who's been cocky? Who is it?
- The fryer is so cocky. - This one.
Hey, fryer. You.
- "Hey, fryer." - Please teach it a lesson.
Why do you keep acting cocky? Why do you keep turning off?
Are you a safety device or what?
Hey, fryer.
I think it's for safety.
In that case, thank you.
(Basic kitchen safety: the fryer turns off...)
(after reaching the set temperature to prevent overheating.)
Are you trying to be funny?
(After teaching the fryer a lesson,)
That's a bit...
Why? It's cute.
It should be longer.
(the floor manager cheerfully makes ades with the part-timer.)
For some reason, a drama comes to mind...
because I'm working with Kyung Soo.
A drama with a situationship while working part-time.
You know what I'm saying. Right, Kyung Soo?
- Kyung Soo, today... - Please stir it for me.
Gosh. Seriously.
(Shutting down the skit at once)
Where are you going after this, Kyung Soo?
Are you taking the subway or the bus?
I'm going to walk.
What is that?
Can I walk with you?
- My mom's picking me up. - Darn it.
- Excuse me. - Okay.
(Meanwhile, at the counter)
Excuse me. Do you have an apron?
- An apron? - Yes.
I'm sorry, but we don't have aprons available.
- Would you like mine? - No. Thank you anyway.
- Would you like my apron? - No, it's okay.
- Ma'am? - Thank you.
I don't know if we have aprons for customers.
Let me give this first.
(She grabs aprons for employees in the pantry.)
Ma'am?
- How about this? - My gosh.
Actually,
this was worn by Head Chef Lee Young Ji...
when she was making...
original tteokbokki with all her soul.
- Is that 1? - Do you need 4?
- No, it's okay. - Only I need it.
Please wait.
- No. - It's really okay.
- Please wait. - We really don't need it.
(New customers arrive on the 1st floor.)
- Welcome. Hello. - My goodness.
My goodness.
(Laughing)
I'm getting a little jealous.
Let me go and see.
- Hello. - Hello.
No one is exclaiming.
I'm getting jealous.
(Server 1, pushed aside by the customers)
Who looks good with cool colours?
(Gasping)
- Do you look good with cool colours? - I'm sorry.
Sure. Thank you.
Let me see.
We even make sure that...
- Your service is amazing. - even your outfits stay spotless.
Thank you.
"I love you as much as the space." Two, three.
I love you as much as the space.
Thank you, everyone.
- Who asked for the apron? - Hey.
- I'm really sorry about that. - Goodness.
(We hope that they work it out amicably.)
This is unbelievable.
Ye Seul, I figured this out.
(With her mind at ease, the rice cake buns look beautiful.)
I have nothing much to do right now.
(It's very relaxing in the kitchen.)
I have nothing to do.
(However...)
(Were you looking for hardship?)
- Mi Hyun. - Yes?
What do I do? It turned very dark.
I put it in for one minute.
(Yu Jin is making pizza.)
Gosh, this is a disaster.
(Mine got stuck.)
- Is it in slow motion? - Yes.
(Happy-go-lucky customers)
It's because this is bigger.
It won't stick if you put it vertically.
(Pay attention to me too.)
It's okay. What should we do about this?
Should I cut it...
- instead? - Instead?
To save part of it.
Shall we do that?
(Coming up next)
(Getting fired up for the business)
(How many batches of prep are you making?)
(25 batches)
(Fully prepared for a flawless service)
(It's going so smoothly.)
(Now she's worried because they're too good.)
(Someone, please mess up the order!)
(The moment she says it)
(A complaint strikes when they're off guard.)
(The head chef rushes into action.)
(It was completely my fault.)
(As always, an unexpected variable shows up.)
(And someone is watching this whole situation unfold.)
(The service goes on for now...)
(Respond)
(Young Ji, the tables have turned...)
(Looking cautiously)
(Watching with a hawk's eye)
(Another mistake is discovered.)
(In the end, the stove gets taken away.)
(The kitchen power dynamic gets flipped.)
What's wrong with you?
(You're too slow.)
(Is the head chef's position in danger?)
(And so begins)
(Head chef versus director)
(A competition of who grills the dough fastest)
(A battle for the pride of the master chefs)
(This isn't dough.)
(Even the members turn away in disappointment.)
(Should I just do it?)
(Upset)
(Will the head chef be able to protect her status?)
(Space Rice Cake)